const level17questions = [
     
    {
        "question": "11 x 3 = ?",
        "options": ["96", "65", "42", "33"],
        "answer": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "83 x 6 = ?",
        "options": ["826", "498", "652", "498"],
        "answer": "498"
    },
    {
        "question": "24 x 9 = ?",
        "options": ["216", "91", "151", "216"],
        "answer": "216"
    },
    {
        "question": "79 x 6 = ?",
        "options": ["780", "474", "484", "474"],
        "answer": "474"
    },
    {
        "question": "66 x 6 = ?",
        "options": ["294", "412", "396", "396"],
        "answer": "396"
    },
    {
        "question": "47 x 9 = ?",
        "options": ["423", "431", "210", "423"],
        "answer": "423"
    },
    {
        "question": "79 x 7 = ?",
        "options": ["741", "344", "139", "553"],
        "answer": "553"
    },
    {
        "question": "91 x 4 = ?",
        "options": ["364", "93", "289", "364"],
        "answer": "364"
    },
    {
        "question": "18 x 3 = ?",
        "options": ["128", "134", "54", "54"],
        "answer": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "78 x 5 = ?",
        "options": ["390", "580", "633", "390"],
        "answer": "390"
    },
    {
        "question": "30 x 7 = ?",
        "options": ["122", "153", "121", "210"],
        "answer": "210"
    },
    {
        "question": "89 x 2 = ?",
        "options": ["141", "227", "178", "178"],
        "answer": "178"
    },
    {
        "question": "57 x 4 = ?",
        "options": ["398", "282", "228", "228"],
        "answer": "228"
    },
    {
        "question": "95 x 5 = ?",
        "options": ["933", "475", "455", "475"],
        "answer": "475"
    },
    {
        "question": "65 x 4 = ?",
        "options": ["260", "220", "631", "260"],
        "answer": "260"
    },
    {
        "question": "29 x 5 = ?",
        "options": ["270", "185", "108", "145"],
        "answer": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "28 x 8 = ?",
        "options": ["34", "104", "174", "224"],
        "answer": "224"
    },
    {
        "question": "70 x 4 = ?",
        "options": ["591", "130", "280", "280"],
        "answer": "280"
    },
    {
        "question": "90 x 2 = ?",
        "options": ["270", "338", "180", "180"],
        "answer": "180"
    },
    {
        "question": "67 x 9 = ?",
        "options": ["603", "658", "590", "603"],
        "answer": "603"
    },
    {
        "question": "36 x 5 = ?",
        "options": ["287", "180", "131", "180"],
        "answer": "180"
    },
    {
        "question": "71 x 6 = ?",
        "options": ["270", "690", "540", "426"],
        "answer": "426"
    },
    {
        "question": "53 x 9 = ?",
        "options": ["226", "477", "118", "477"],
        "answer": "477"
    },
    {
        "question": "99 x 5 = ?",
        "options": ["270", "874", "495", "495"],
        "answer": "495"
    },
    {
        "question": "89 x 3 = ?",
        "options": ["584", "267", "693", "267"],
        "answer": "267"
    },

{
    question: "44 x 8 = ?",
    options: ["352", "434", "91", "248"],
    answer: "352",
  },
  {
    question: "63 x 9 = ?",
    options: ["395", "86", "489", "567"],
    answer: "567",
  },
  {
    question: "53 x 9 = ?",
    options: ["133", "477", "270", "152"],
    answer: "477",
  },
  {
    question: "56 x 5 = ?",
    options: ["280", "433", "279", "147"],
    answer: "280",
  },
  {
    question: "66 x 9 = ?",
    options: ["594", "334", "561", "257"],
    answer: "594",
  },
  {
    question: "19 x 6 = ?",
    options: ["115", "114", "40", "181"],
    answer: "114",
  },
  {
    question: "25 x 6 = ?",
    options: ["128", "109", "72", "150"],
    answer: "150",
  },
  {
    question: "38 x 5 = ?",
    options: ["190", "336", "298", "272"],
    answer: "190",
  },
  {
    question: "16 x 2 = ?",
    options: ["146", "32", "46", "88"],
    answer: "32",
  },
  {
    question: "22 x 2 = ?",
    options: ["124", "132", "44", "49"],
    answer: "44",
  },
  {
    question: "65 x 3 = ?",
    options: ["68", "274", "195", "306"],
    answer: "195",
  },
  {
    question: "91 x 9 = ?",
    options: ["594", "819", "490", "319"],
    answer: "819",
  },
  {
    question: "44 x 3 = ?",
    options: ["339", "132", "299", "273"],
    answer: "132",
  },
  {
    question: "40 x 6 = ?",
    options: ["65", "240", "364", "257"],
    answer: "240",
  },
  {
    question: "91 x 6 = ?",
    options: ["342", "546", "509", "868"],
    answer: "546",
  },
  {
    question: "89 x 7 = ?",
    options: ["563", "623", "720", "533"],
    answer: "623",
  },
  {
    question: "27 x 5 = ?",
    options: ["172", "135", "186", "190"],
    answer: "135",
  },
  {
    question: "98 x 8 = ?",
    options: ["212", "784", "177", "216"],
    answer: "784",
  },
  {
    question: "69 x 5 = ?",
    options: ["181", "345", "451", "236"],
    answer: "345",
  },
  {
    question: "33 x 9 = ?",
    options: ["123", "184", "112", "297"],
    answer: "297",
  },
  {
    question: "43 x 4 = ?",
    options: ["203", "172", "167", "348"],
    answer: "172",
  },
  {
    question: "50 x 8 = ?",
    options: ["313", "400", "137", "148"],
    answer: "400",
  },
  {
    question: "56 x 7 = ?",
    options: ["477", "385", "392", "523"],
    answer: "392",
  },
  {
    question: "76 x 6 = ?",
    options: ["329", "456", "203", "602"],
    answer: "456",
  },
  {
    question: "91 x 4 = ?",
    options: ["649", "364", "311", "455"],
    answer: "364",
  },

{
        "question": "13 x 5 = ?",
        "options": ["65", "123", "51", "65"],
        "answer": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "80 x 3 = ?",
        "options": ["579", "359", "240", "240"],
        "answer": "240"
    },
    {
        "question": "31 x 6 = ?",
        "options": ["186", "264", "261", "186"],
        "answer": "186"
    },
    {
        "question": "68 x 5 = ?",
        "options": ["340", "413", "142", "340"],
        "answer": "340"
    },
    {
        "question": "78 x 9 = ?",
        "options": ["702", "370", "695", "702"],
        "answer": "702"
    },
    {
        "question": "31 x 6 = ?",
        "options": ["185", "284", "186", "186"],
        "answer": "186"
    },
    {
        "question": "42 x 9 = ?",
        "options": ["376", "226", "302", "378"],
        "answer": "378"
    },
    {
        "question": "16 x 6 = ?",
        "options": ["96", "17", "105", "96"],
        "answer": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "86 x 9 = ?",
        "options": ["774", "856", "796", "774"],
        "answer": "774"
    },
    {
        "question": "69 x 5 = ?",
        "options": ["382", "345", "259", "345"],
        "answer": "345"
    },
    {
        "question": "62 x 4 = ?",
        "options": ["248", "478", "321", "248"],
        "answer": "248"
    },
    {
        "question": "81 x 9 = ?",
        "options": ["698", "369", "729", "729"],
        "answer": "729"
    },
    {
        "question": "18 x 4 = ?",
        "options": ["72", "169", "165", "72"],
        "answer": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "98 x 2 = ?",
        "options": ["692", "661", "196", "196"],
        "answer": "196"
    },
    {
        "question": "27 x 9 = ?",
        "options": ["243", "107", "148", "243"],
        "answer": "243"
    },
    {
        "question": "73 x 8 = ?",
        "options": ["641", "321", "584", "584"],
        "answer": "584"
    },
    {
        "question": "20 x 9 = ?",
        "options": ["174", "180", "92", "180"],
        "answer": "180"
    },
    {
        "question": "40 x 3 = ?",
        "options": ["219", "253", "120", "120"],
        "answer": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "95 x 7 = ?",
        "options": ["665", "273", "757", "665"],
        "answer": "665"
    },
    {
        "question": "84 x 3 = ?",
        "options": ["276", "252", "461", "252"],
        "answer": "252"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 x 3 = ?",
        "options": ["42", "16", "107", "42"],
        "answer": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "35 x 5 = ?",
        "options": ["175", "89", "93", "175"],
        "answer": "175"
    },
    {
        "question": "45 x 8 = ?",
        "options": ["423", "174", "285", "360"],
        "answer": "360"
    },
    {
        "question": "29 x 4 = ?",
        "options": ["182", "115", "116", "116"],
        "answer": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "80 x 2 = ?",
        "options": ["646", "160", "737", "160"],
        "answer": "160"
    },

 {
        "question": "13 x 2 = ?",
        "options": ["27", "21", "26", "26"],
        "answer": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "94 x 5 = ?",
        "options": ["470", "270", "453", "470"],
        "answer": "470"
    },
    {
        "question": "89 x 2 = ?",
        "options": ["561", "178", "182", "178"],
        "answer": "178"
    },
    {
        "question": "48 x 9 = ?",
        "options": ["463", "405", "432", "432"],
        "answer": "432"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 x 7 = ?",
        "options": ["116", "76", "105", "105"],
        "answer": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "21 x 9 = ?",
        "options": ["199", "189", "126", "189"],
        "answer": "189"
    },
    {
        "question": "77 x 3 = ?",
        "options": ["152", "231", "233", "231"],
        "answer": "231"
    },
    {
        "question": "13 x 3 = ?",
        "options": ["69", "39", "56", "39"],
        "answer": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "22 x 7 = ?",
        "options": ["41", "192", "188", "154"],
        "answer": "154"
    },
    {
        "question": "32 x 2 = ?",
        "options": ["127", "100", "55", "64"],
        "answer": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "34 x 5 = ?",
        "options": ["80", "170", "243", "170"],
        "answer": "170"
    },
    {
        "question": "66 x 5 = ?",
        "options": ["561", "653", "94", "330"],
        "answer": "330"
    },
    {
        "question": "58 x 7 = ?",
        "options": ["312", "406", "69", "406"],
        "answer": "406"
    },
    {
        "question": "89 x 4 = ?",
        "options": ["835", "356", "444", "356"],
        "answer": "356"
    },
    {
        "question": "92 x 2 = ?",
        "options": ["898", "365", "184", "184"],
        "answer": "184"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 x 9 = ?",
        "options": ["133", "96", "135", "135"],
        "answer": "135"
    },
    {
        "question": "22 x 5 = ?",
        "options": ["89", "110", "188", "110"],
        "answer": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "80 x 6 = ?",
        "options": ["342", "480", "703", "480"],
        "answer": "480"
    },
    {
        "question": "46 x 9 = ?",
        "options": ["414", "77", "420", "414"],
        "answer": "414"
    },
    {
        "question": "60 x 5 = ?",
        "options": ["372", "349", "121", "300"],
        "answer": "300"
    },
    {
        "question": "28 x 9 = ?",
        "options": ["105", "179", "252", "252"],
        "answer": "252"
    },
    {
        "question": "63 x 9 = ?",
        "options": ["153", "567", "75", "567"],
        "answer": "567"
    },
    {
        "question": "76 x 4 = ?",
        "options": ["701", "304", "453", "304"],
        "answer": "304"
    },
    {
        "question": "47 x 2 = ?",
        "options": ["79", "384", "70", "94"],
        "answer": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "32 x 2 = ?",
        "options": ["107", "117", "133", "64"],
        "answer": "64"
    },

{
        question: "321 x 8 = ?",
        options: ["2368", "2498", "2568", "2105"],
        answer: "2568"
    },
    {
        question: "475 x 3 = ?",
        options: ["1398", "1777", "2257", "1425"],
        answer: "1425"
    },
    {
        question: "493 x 2 = ?",
        options: ["1881", "2257", "986", "4287"],
        answer: "986"
    },
    {
        question: "882 x 5 = ?",
        options: ["4192", "5100", "4410", "6232"],
        answer: "4410"
    },
    {
        question: "709 x 7 = ?",
        options: ["2590", "1992", "4963", "3684"],
        answer: "4963"
    },
    {
        question: "558 x 6 = ?",
        options: ["5498", "3348", "3500", "1289"],
        answer: "3348"
    },
    {
        question: "652 x 5 = ?",
        options: ["2543", "1571", "3260", "720"],
        answer: "3260"
    },
    {
        question: "856 x 2 = ?",
        options: ["2093", "2541", "6150", "1712"],
        answer: "1712"
    },
    {
        question: "610 x 9 = ?",
        options: ["3445", "5490", "5903", "2801"],
        answer: "5490"
    },
    {
        question: "153 x 9 = ?",
        options: ["1377", "375", "1418", "1121"],
        answer: "1377"
    },
    {
        question: "789 x 9 = ?",
        options: ["940", "7101", "4259", "7806"],
        answer: "7101"
    },
    {
        question: "612 x 7 = ?",
        options: ["6066", "6059", "5148", "4284"],
        answer: "4284"
    },
    {
        question: "212 x 7 = ?",
        options: ["1484", "1357", "493", "216"],
        answer: "1484"
    },
    {
        question: "383 x 5 = ?",
        options: ["2427", "2453", "1292", "1915"],
        answer: "1915"
    },
    {
        question: "414 x 7 = ?",
        options: ["2898", "546", "3611", "3915"],
        answer: "2898"
    },
    {
        question: "973 x 5 = ?",
        options: ["8273", "6423", "5690", "4865"],
        answer: "4865"
    },
    {
        question: "995 x 6 = ?",
        options: ["7106", "5970", "6118", "4773"],
        answer: "5970"
    },
    {
        question: "552 x 4 = ?",
        options: ["1516", "2208", "2904", "1090"],
        answer: "2208"
    },
    {
        question: "399 x 6 = ?",
        options: ["3947", "2394", "2062", "2963"],
        answer: "2394"
    },
    {
        question: "477 x 9 = ?",
        options: ["4293", "3403", "1462", "2892"],
        answer: "4293"
    },
    {
        question: "180 x 8 = ?",
        options: ["916", "1440", "1729", "350"],
        answer: "1440"
    },
    {
        question: "462 x 6 = ?",
        options: ["2441", "4463", "2772", "2871"],
        answer: "2772"
    },
    {
        question: "706 x 5 = ?",
        options: ["4467", "3530", "2195", "3939"],
        answer: "3530"
    },
    {
        question: "874 x 2 = ?",
        options: ["1748", "8297", "5614", "3715"],
        answer: "1748"
    },
    {
        question: "348 x 8 = ?",
        options: ["1878", "3453", "2634", "2784"],
        answer: "2784"
    },

{
        question: "337 x 3 = ?",
        options: ["362", "718", "2980", "1011"],
        answer: "1011"
    },
    {
        question: "173 x 2 = ?",
        options: ["511", "733", "290", "346"],
        answer: "346"
    },
    {
        question: "765 x 7 = ?",
        options: ["4554", "5355", "6299", "5849"],
        answer: "5355"
    },
    {
        question: "914 x 6 = ?",
        options: ["3513", "7219", "8770", "5484"],
        answer: "5484"
    },
    {
        question: "376 x 8 = ?",
        options: ["2363", "1976", "3008", "2224"],
        answer: "3008"
    },
    {
        question: "906 x 5 = ?",
        options: ["8827", "4530", "5269", "2090"],
        answer: "4530"
    },
    {
        question: "723 x 7 = ?",
        options: ["6021", "5061", "3558", "4983"],
        answer: "5061"
    },
    {
        question: "275 x 7 = ?",
        options: ["1925", "1000", "914", "2472"],
        answer: "1925"
    },
    {
        question: "167 x 8 = ?",
        options: ["1336", "1351", "637", "412"],
        answer: "1336"
    },
    {
        question: "883 x 9 = ?",
        options: ["2378", "8480", "7947", "7047"],
        answer: "7947"
    },
    {
        question: "683 x 5 = ?",
        options: ["3415", "2186", "6647", "5738"],
        answer: "3415"
    },
    {
        question: "206 x 5 = ?",
        options: ["1838", "1480", "1157", "1030"],
        answer: "1030"
    },
    {
        question: "563 x 7 = ?",
        options: ["2228", "771", "3941", "755"],
        answer: "3941"
    },
    {
        question: "112 x 5 = ?",
        options: ["689", "925", "560", "410"],
        answer: "560"
    },
    {
        question: "367 x 6 = ?",
        options: ["3144", "1285", "1258", "2202"],
        answer: "2202"
    },
    {
        question: "775 x 7 = ?",
        options: ["3610", "5425", "4256", "6609"],
        answer: "5425"
    },
    {
        question: "918 x 7 = ?",
        options: ["3029", "6426", "4608", "3551"],
        answer: "6426"
    },
    {
        question: "707 x 8 = ?",
        options: ["4897", "5656", "4348", "2973"],
        answer: "5656"
    },
    {
        question: "388 x 8 = ?",
        options: ["3104", "2039", "1979", "1557"],
        answer: "3104"
    },
    {
        question: "596 x 3 = ?",
        options: ["2258", "5619", "4754", "1788"],
        answer: "1788"
    },
    {
        question: "229 x 3 = ?",
        options: ["687", "1510", "1236", "308"],
        answer: "687"
    },
    {
        question: "512 x 5 = ?",
        options: ["2792", "2560", "4780", "1861"],
        answer: "2560"
    },
    {
        question: "901 x 4 = ?",
        options: ["4779", "4809", "3168", "3604"],
        answer: "3604"
    },
    {
        question: "588 x 5 = ?",
        options: ["3775", "2940", "2883", "1680"],
        answer: "2940"
    },
    {
        question: "725 x 4 = ?",
        options: ["5524", "2642", "2900", "3218"],
        answer: "2900"
    },

{
        question: "181 x 9 = ?",
        options: ["1408", "1241", "1629", "1709"],
        answer: "1629"
    },
    {
        question: "818 x 3 = ?",
        options: ["2388", "5707", "2454", "7512"],
        answer: "2454"
    },
    {
        question: "786 x 6 = ?",
        options: ["4716", "1327", "6668", "4516"],
        answer: "4716"
    },
    {
        question: "730 x 9 = ?",
        options: ["3158", "6570", "6120", "6603"],
        answer: "6570"
    },
    {
        question: "170 x 5 = ?",
        options: ["995", "1625", "313", "850"],
        answer: "850"
    },
    {
        question: "277 x 4 = ?",
        options: ["1108", "581", "2455", "1304"],
        answer: "1108"
    },
    {
        question: "246 x 4 = ?",
        options: ["2246", "1966", "984", "2379"],
        answer: "984"
    },
    {
        question: "635 x 7 = ?",
        options: ["666", "1323", "4445", "4908"],
        answer: "4445"
    },
    {
        question: "294 x 9 = ?",
        options: ["2646", "2148", "2300", "2467"],
        answer: "2646"
    },
    {
        question: "373 x 8 = ?",
        options: ["1885", "1110", "1922", "2984"],
        answer: "2984"
    },
    {
        question: "707 x 8 = ?",
        options: ["3627", "4978", "5656", "1541"],
        answer: "5656"
    },
    {
        question: "456 x 9 = ?",
        options: ["3830", "2110", "4104", "2803"],
        answer: "4104"
    },
    {
        question: "748 x 7 = ?",
        options: ["5752", "5854", "5236", "6929"],
        answer: "5236"
    },
    {
        question: "348 x 8 = ?",
        options: ["2843", "663", "354", "2784"],
        answer: "2784"
    },
    {
        question: "102 x 9 = ?",
        options: ["860", "666", "747", "918"],
        answer: "918"
    },
    {
        question: "774 x 7 = ?",
        options: ["3177", "5418", "5736", "6535"],
        answer: "5418"
    },
    {
        question: "534 x 7 = ?",
        options: ["3738", "669", "2435", "897"],
        answer: "3738"
    },
    {
        question: "920 x 7 = ?",
        options: ["2419", "2808", "6440", "7712"],
        answer: "6440"
    },
    {
        question: "251 x 4 = ?",
        options: ["1004", "1532", "1685", "2492"],
        answer: "1004"
    },
    {
        question: "227 x 2 = ?",
        options: ["1132", "948", "1343", "454"],
        answer: "454"
    },
    {
        question: "798 x 9 = ?",
        options: ["4752", "7182", "4076", "5163"],
        answer: "7182"
    },
    {
        question: "188 x 9 = ?",
        options: ["1667", "762", "1293", "1692"],
        answer: "1692"
    },
    {
        question: "818 x 5 = ?",
        options: ["7151", "5038", "4090", "4244"],
        answer: "4090"
    },
    {
        question: "664 x 8 = ?",
        options: ["5312", "3561", "5684", "1507"],
        answer: "5312"
    },
    {
        question: "998 x 8 = ?",
        options: ["3461", "6820", "7984", "5885"],
        answer: "7984"
    },

{
        question: "581 x 5 = ?",
        options: ["2905", "4325", "2375", "1669"],
        answer: "2905"
    },
    {
        question: "696 x 9 = ?",
        options: ["5045", "6264", "4450", "5884"],
        answer: "6264"
    },
    {
        question: "500 x 7 = ?",
        options: ["778", "608", "3955", "3500"],
        answer: "3500"
    },
    {
        question: "951 x 4 = ?",
        options: ["1214", "7994", "3804", "4136"],
        answer: "3804"
    },
    {
        question: "500 x 2 = ?",
        options: ["1725", "1000", "3718", "3662"],
        answer: "1000"
    },
    {
        question: "561 x 8 = ?",
        options: ["4488", "5610", "1541", "4293"],
        answer: "4488"
    },
    {
        question: "836 x 3 = ?",
        options: ["6119", "2508", "1924", "2577"],
        answer: "2508"
    },
    {
        question: "313 x 7 = ?",
        options: ["1908", "3102", "2191", "2795"],
        answer: "2191"
    },
    {
        question: "665 x 3 = ?",
        options: ["6487", "4375", "1995", "5324"],
        answer: "1995"
    },
    {
        question: "752 x 9 = ?",
        options: ["6262", "6768", "5773", "3336"],
        answer: "6768"
    },
    {
        question: "132 x 2 = ?",
        options: ["617", "977", "264", "313"],
        answer: "264"
    },
    {
        question: "972 x 3 = ?",
        options: ["7960", "8333", "7854", "2916"],
        answer: "2916"
    },
    {
        question: "219 x 2 = ?",
        options: ["438", "450", "1844", "1652"],
        answer: "438"
    },
    {
        question: "593 x 2 = ?",
        options: ["3076", "2967", "1186", "5161"],
        answer: "1186"
    },
    {
        question: "372 x 8 = ?",
        options: ["2598", "2976", "1557", "1539"],
        answer: "2976"
    },
    {
        question: "854 x 7 = ?",
        options: ["5978", "2510", "3838", "2023"],
        answer: "5978"
    },
    {
        question: "591 x 7 = ?",
        options: ["4137", "3385", "4194", "2853"],
        answer: "4137"
    },
    {
        question: "371 x 4 = ?",
        options: ["2802", "2494", "1484", "842"],
        answer: "1484"
    },
    {
        question: "212 x 6 = ?",
        options: ["777", "1272", "263", "378"],
        answer: "1272"
    },
    {
        question: "517 x 2 = ?",
        options: ["1034", "659", "2174", "2464"],
        answer: "1034"
    },
    {
        question: "660 x 5 = ?",
        options: ["3675", "3928", "2669", "3300"],
        answer: "3300"
    },
    {
        question: "743 x 5 = ?",
        options: ["5141", "3715", "1013", "5970"],
        answer: "3715"
    },
    {
        question: "704 x 4 = ?",
        options: ["1145", "979", "2816", "4665"],
        answer: "2816"
    },
    {
        question: "547 x 6 = ?",
        options: ["3025", "2702", "3282", "5255"],
        answer: "3282"
    },
    {
        question: "815 x 5 = ?",
        options: ["6135", "2118", "4075", "2254"],
        answer: "4075"
    },

{
        question: "815 x 5 = ?",
        options: ["6135", "2118", "4075", "2254"],
        answer: "4075"
    },
    {
        question: "3301 x 2 = ?",
        options: ["6602", "29179", "7620", "14660"],
        answer: "6602"
    },
    {
        question: "4159 x 5 = ?",
        options: ["15017", "20795", "9333", "26151"],
        answer: "20795"
    },
    {
        question: "5008 x 4 = ?",
        options: ["43777", "31161", "47916", "20032"],
        answer: "20032"
    },
    {
        question: "7775 x 5 = ?",
        options: ["44024", "41781", "38875", "49300"],
        answer: "38875"
    },
    {
        question: "7632 x 5 = ?",
        options: ["46532", "48237", "26210", "38160"],
        answer: "38160"
    },
    {
        question: "9649 x 4 = ?",
        options: ["44872", "47274", "60270", "38596"],
        answer: "38596"
    },
    {
        question: "7263 x 7 = ?",
        options: ["12981", "50841", "49642", "42837"],
        answer: "50841"
    },
    {
        question: "3709 x 3 = ?",
        options: ["28246", "25559", "28135", "11127"],
        answer: "11127"
    },
    {
        question: "4530 x 9 = ?",
        options: ["8920", "40770", "23857", "42275"],
        answer: "40770"
    },
    {
        question: "2566 x 2 = ?",
        options: ["22129", "17763", "21898", "5132"],
        answer: "5132"
    },
    {
        question: "5972 x 7 = ?",
        options: ["28674", "41804", "22655", "28909"],
        answer: "41804"
    },
    {
        question: "6171 x 3 = ?",
        options: ["18513", "49596", "48845", "53481"],
        answer: "18513"
    },
    {
        question: "9348 x 9 = ?",
        options: ["26447", "84132", "63537", "32101"],
        answer: "84132"
    },
    {
        question: "1188 x 8 = ?",
        options: ["9504", "9860", "11345", "2830"],
        answer: "9504"
    },
    {
        question: "1577 x 3 = ?",
        options: ["4731", "12110", "14142", "6733"],
        answer: "4731"
    },
    {
        question: "5245 x 2 = ?",
        options: ["26506", "10490", "18063", "30209"],
        answer: "10490"
    },
    {
        question: "7765 x 3 = ?",
        options: ["64351", "23295", "43661", "14571"],
        answer: "23295"
    },
    {
        question: "9282 x 8 = ?",
        options: ["38764", "48860", "74256", "84104"],
        answer: "74256"
    },
    {
        question: "3875 x 4 = ?",
        options: ["37528", "15500", "18927", "28946"],
        answer: "15500"
    },
    {
        question: "8164 x 9 = ?",
        options: ["64250", "73476", "8678", "26889"],
        answer: "73476"
    },
    {
        question: "9576 x 9 = ?",
        options: ["86184", "92735", "56024", "59848"],
        answer: "86184"
    },
    {
        question: "2396 x 9 = ?",
        options: ["6294", "17073", "18797", "21564"],
        answer: "21564"
    },
    {
        question: "1074 x 2 = ?",
        options: ["2110", "8417", "2148", "4789"],
        answer: "2148"
    },
    {
        question: "2801 x 5 = ?",
        options: ["27687", "26318", "14005", "7757"],
        answer: "14005"
    },
    {
        question: "4391 x 2 = ?",
        options: ["40037", "9464", "33010", "8782"],
        answer: "8782"
    },

{
        question: "3772 x 4 = ?",
        options: ["18977", "15088", "27427", "37509"],
        answer: "15088"
    },
    {
        question: "8944 x 2 = ?",
        options: ["16979", "17888", "78972", "85377"],
        answer: "17888"
    },
    {
        question: "5661 x 5 = ?",
        options: ["28305", "45394", "53231", "11236"],
        answer: "28305"
    },
    {
        question: "2122 x 4 = ?",
        options: ["8488", "15961", "17023", "19001"],
        answer: "8488"
    },
    {
        question: "6599 x 7 = ?",
        options: ["46153", "46193", "51685", "54163"],
        answer: "46193"
    },
    {
        question: "4131 x 5 = ?",
        options: ["20655", "13372", "38276", "4791"],
        answer: "20655"
    },
    {
        question: "8775 x 6 = ?",
        options: ["17449", "42106", "52650", "59940"],
        answer: "52650"
    },
    {
        question: "4224 x 5 = ?",
        options: ["10222", "17347", "21120", "37218"],
        answer: "21120"
    },
    {
        question: "9784 x 2 = ?",
        options: ["19568", "44854", "70747", "90909"],
        answer: "19568"
    },
    {
        question: "9407 x 5 = ?",
        options: ["47035", "51817", "57466", "62325"],
        answer: "47035"
    },
    {
        question: "3987 x 8 = ?",
        options: ["25593", "25649", "31236", "31896"],
        answer: "31896"
    },
    {
        question: "8342 x 5 = ?",
        options: ["29487", "33570", "41710", "79518"],
        answer: "41710"
    },
    {
        question: "5139 x 4 = ?",
        options: ["12056", "15685", "20556", "39023"],
        answer: "20556"
    },
    {
        question: "1433 x 2 = ?",
        options: ["2866", "5938", "6705", "13353"],
        answer: "2866"
    },
    {
        question: "9381 x 9 = ?",
        options: ["27759", "58520", "62765", "84429"],
        answer: "84429"
    },
    {
        question: "4081 x 3 = ?",
        options: ["8284", "11213", "12243", "35095"],
        answer: "12243"
    },
    {
        question: "5130 x 7 = ?",
        options: ["21645", "32082", "35910", "43113"],
        answer: "35910"
    },
    {
        question: "9723 x 3 = ?",
        options: ["29169", "51549", "58172", "69571"],
        answer: "29169"
    },
    {
        question: "4360 x 5 = ?",
        options: ["17313", "18222", "20589", "21800"],
        answer: "21800"
    },
    {
        question: "6130 x 2 = ?",
        options: ["7578", "12260", "24597", "50283"],
        answer: "12260"
    },
    {
        question: "9809 x 5 = ?",
        options: ["42190", "49045", "59350", "42050"],
        answer: "49045"
    },
    {
        question: "3410 x 5 = ?",
        options: ["17050", "30472", "33377", "7044"],
        answer: "17050"
    },
    {
        question: "6005 x 3 = ?",
        options: ["18015", "20854", "34700", "38782"],
        answer: "18015"
    },
    {
        question: "8486 x 3 = ?",
        options: ["25458", "30633", "58430", "74936"],
        answer: "25458"
    },
    {
        question: "1608 x 2 = ?",
        options: ["3216", "7339", "15263", "15498"],
        answer: "3216"
    },

{
        question: "4246 x 6 = ?",
        options: ["25476", "40363", "32233", "19746"],
        answer: "25476"
    },
    {
        question: "1917 x 2 = ?",
        options: ["16973", "3834", "2546", "5674"],
        answer: "3834"
    },
    {
        question: "2503 x 7 = ?",
        options: ["20254", "17521", "24079", "13650"],
        answer: "17521"
    },
    {
        question: "4955 x 3 = ?",
        options: ["18629", "14865", "23000", "7694"],
        answer: "14865"
    },
    {
        question: "9203 x 6 = ?",
        options: ["43533", "12500", "55218", "80125"],
        answer: "55218"
    },
    {
        question: "8319 x 4 = ?",
        options: ["51834", "33276", "66934", "72439"],
        answer: "33276"
    },
    {
        question: "2683 x 6 = ?",
        options: ["9958", "16098", "25660", "3953"],
        answer: "16098"
    },
    {
        question: "8327 x 3 = ?",
        options: ["15809", "24981", "67829", "35302"],
        answer: "24981"
    },
    {
        question: "9028 x 2 = ?",
        options: ["42820", "18056", "57342", "20562"],
        answer: "18056"
    },
    {
        question: "1371 x 2 = ?",
        options: ["4406", "8698", "2414", "2742"],
        answer: "2742"
    },
    {
        question: "6754 x 2 = ?",
        options: ["17530", "55174", "13508", "57068"],
        answer: "13508"
    },
    {
        question: "1455 x 4 = ?",
        options: ["5820", "12640", "10619", "6325"],
        answer: "5820"
    },
    {
        question: "7501 x 3 = ?",
        options: ["22503", "12606", "67740", "33352"],
        answer: "22503"
    },
    {
        question: "1897 x 2 = ?",
        options: ["5178", "14766", "10248", "3794"],
        answer: "3794"
    },
    {
        question: "4986 x 3 = ?",
        options: ["14958", "18062", "35095", "30515"],
        answer: "14958"
    },
    {
        question: "2037 x 6 = ?",
        options: ["4677", "12222", "8277", "15432"],
        answer: "12222"
    },
    {
        question: "3791 x 6 = ?",
        options: ["22746", "36763", "17746", "15901"],
        answer: "22746"
    },
    {
        question: "2303 x 4 = ?",
        options: ["14545", "12113", "9878", "9212"],
        answer: "9212"
    },
    {
        question: "7633 x 7 = ?",
        options: ["33556", "17142", "53431", "28282"],
        answer: "53431"
    },
    {
        question: "9132 x 2 = ?",
        options: ["63196", "18264", "35705", "53869"],
        answer: "18264"
    },
    {
        question: "2976 x 3 = ?",
        options: ["4621", "22782", "10582", "8928"],
        answer: "8928"
    },
    {
        question: "4892 x 5 = ?",
        options: ["5250", "6857", "33416", "24460"],
        answer: "24460"
    },
    {
        question: "8658 x 3 = ?",
        options: ["25974", "51398", "32149", "28395"],
        answer: "25974"
    },
    {
        question: "3752 x 6 = ?",
        options: ["22512", "6973", "29325", "12466"],
        answer: "22512"
    },
    {
        question: "3575 x 2 = ?",
        options: ["7553", "7150", "30520", "32192"],
        answer: "7150"
    },

{
        question: "6034 x 8 = ?",
        options: ["41503", "48272", "57072", "10097"],
        answer: "48272"
    },
    {
        question: "7406 x 8 = ?",
        options: ["15664", "59248", "13395", "35718"],
        answer: "59248"
    },
    {
        question: "3535 x 9 = ?",
        options: ["22513", "25758", "9262", "31815"],
        answer: "31815"
    },
    {
        question: "4883 x 6 = ?",
        options: ["9912", "29298", "25875", "11742"],
        answer: "29298"
    },
    {
        question: "2786 x 4 = ?",
        options: ["11144", "25356", "26750", "7123"],
        answer: "11144"
    },
    {
        question: "9506 x 4 = ?",
        options: ["34321", "38024", "72533", "29538"],
        answer: "38024"
    },
    {
        question: "3003 x 9 = ?",
        options: ["27027", "15462", "5388", "20935"],
        answer: "27027"
    },
    {
        question: "2747 x 9 = ?",
        options: ["24723", "21856", "22760", "27078"],
        answer: "24723"
    },
    {
        question: "2289 x 3 = ?",
        options: ["18279", "20244", "3117", "6867"],
        answer: "6867"
    },
    {
        question: "9929 x 8 = ?",
        options: ["79432", "54103", "67463", "31133"],
        answer: "79432"
    },
    {
        question: "8554 x 9 = ?",
        options: ["29983", "36776", "76986", "57866"],
        answer: "76986"
    },
    {
        question: "1680 x 7 = ?",
        options: ["4278", "1907", "11760", "14899"],
        answer: "11760"
    },
    {
        question: "1929 x 7 = ?",
        options: ["8002", "10812", "13503", "18713"],
        answer: "13503"
    },
    {
        question: "2522 x 3 = ?",
        options: ["7566", "3393", "21638", "11514"],
        answer: "7566"
    },
    {
        question: "8268 x 3 = ?",
        options: ["24804", "44619", "77539", "33786"],
        answer: "24804"
    },
    {
        question: "6038 x 6 = ?",
        options: ["20576", "45469", "12776", "36228"],
        answer: "36228"
    },
    {
        question: "2174 x 3 = ?",
        options: ["5795", "11079", "6287", "6522"],
        answer: "6522"
    },
    {
        question: "1446 x 8 = ?",
        options: ["13071", "5855", "13505", "11568"],
        answer: "11568"
    },
    {
        question: "2027 x 8 = ?",
        options: ["16216", "5475", "7361", "19795"],
        answer: "16216"
    },
    {
        question: "3440 x 9 = ?",
        options: ["30960", "24571", "28227", "6062"],
        answer: "30960"
    },
    {
        question: "8459 x 7 = ?",
        options: ["33217", "59213", "56647", "46268"],
        answer: "59213"
    },
    {
        question: "4760 x 4 = ?",
        options: ["24079", "24765", "27628", "19040"],
        answer: "19040"
    },
    {
        question: "9528 x 4 = ?",
        options: ["69875", "38112", "26666", "39547"],
        answer: "38112"
    },
    {
        question: "4143 x 8 = ?",
        options: ["38788", "33144", "21077", "38257"],
        answer: "33144"
    },
    {
        question: "2986 x 5 = ?",
        options: ["29080", "14930", "10592", "5595"],
        answer: "14930"
    },
];
export default level17questions;